<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stat Tool</string>

    <!-- labels -->
    <string name="choose_affinity">Choose Affinity [Required]</string>
    <string name="choose_card_type">Choose Card Type [Required]</string>
    <string name="spinner_default_txt">Select</string>
    <string name="regenerate">Regenerate</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset To Base Stats?</string>
    <string name="num">/#</string>
    <string name="num_num">/#/#</string>
    <string name="lv">Lv:</string>
    <string name="asc">Asc:</string>
    <string name="hp">HP:</string>
    <string name="str">Str:</string>
    <string name="spd">Spd:</string>
    <string name="wis">Wis:</string>
    <string name="phy_def">Phy Def:</string>
    <string name="mag_def">Mag Def:</string>
    <string name="crit">Crit %:</string>
    <string name="tooltip_default">Start by selecting an Affinity and Card Type to
        generate stats!</string>
    <string name="tooltip_change_lv_and_asc">Change the Lv (level) and Asc (ascension) values to
        see updates to stats</string>
    <string name="tooltip_reset_stats">Reset stats by setting the level to 0</string>
    <string name="tooltip_stats_increase">Stats increase by 5% per Lv (level)</string>
    <string name="tooltip_asc_increase">Increasing Asc (ascension) will increase your man Lv
        (level) by 2</string>
    <string name="tooltip_physical_defense">Guardians with affinity Robotic, Physical or Beast do
        physical damage that is greatly negated by Physical Defense</string>
    <string name="tooltip_magical_defense">Guardians with affinity Elemental, Psychic or Brainiac do
        magical damage that is greatly negated by Magical Defense</string>
    <string name="tooltip_strength_attack">Guardians with affinity Robotic, Physical or Beast rely on
        Str (strength) to deal damage to opponents</string>
    <string name="tooltip_wisdom_attack">Guardians with affinity Elemental, Psychic or Brainiac rely on
        Wis (wisdom) to deal damage to opponents</string>
    <string name="tooltip_critical_attack">Successful crit (critical) attacks will add an additional
        20% bonus damage to overall damage dealt</string>
    <string name="tooltip_stats_regenerate">IMPORTANT: Current stats are outdated! Stats do not regenerate
        automatically. Press the regenerate button to update stats</string>

    <!-- Guardian descriptions -->
    <string name="frost_fire_desc">Burst is a lone wolf and mysterious. With no real name, enemies often call
        her \"Frost Fire\" because her energy weapons spit out blue fire! It is no secret that Burst
        spends her nights roaming the streets looking for bad guys, but what she does with the rest
        of her time is unknown.</string>
    <string name="scourge_desc">Yu Gang can create boiling hot black oil residue, that secretes from his bones.
        He can toss this oil to burn, blind and even immobilize his opponents in a sticky goo that makes it
        nearly impossible to remove.</string>
    <string name="silent_storm">Jarvis Jones is very disciplined and despite having killed hundreds of people his moral
        compass is unfaltering. His intentions are good, they have always been. Even after an assassination.</string>
    <string name="aziza_desc">Sabina has the ability to see future events. Her visions are never fluid, they are patchy
        and generally unclear. She can trigger a vision if needed, but they mostly come randomly and uncontrollably.
        She also has the power to briefly control time, however, this is an ability she has yet to master.</string>
    <string name="binary_desc">Jerik Johnson spends most of his time staring at the computer screen in a zombie-like trance.
        He is passive-aggressive, he rarely gets into physical confrontations. But while in front of his computer,
        he can destroy your life or even erase your entire existence with a couple keystrokes.</string>
    <string name="cougar_desc">Very spiritual and down-to-earth. He is humble but fierce in his attack.
        Earth, life and family are what he loves and values most. He will do all that is required to protect
        everyone who dares to disturb what he stands for. His name translates as \“Cougar\” in English.</string>
    <string name="brick_jaw_desc">As one contemporaneous high-school peer observed, \"Brickjaw has a terrible identity
        problem, a marked inferiority complex and is only comfortable when making others uncomfortable.\" Brickjaw is
        dangerous not because he enjoys fighting, but because he both enjoys it and is very skilled at it.</string>
    <string name="hair_witch_desc">Tera Harkenson has complete control over her hair, allowing her to freely alter,
        grow, change texture, color, shape and manipulate as if it was an appendage. She can weave her hair into
        different shapes, however, she generally uses her hair as additional knife wielding limbs.</string>
    <string name="genesis_desc">Michael is stronger than the average human, but he does not have god-like powers.
        He uses his intelligence, and the initial horror that people have when they witness him to his advantage.
        He knows that he is not immune to death and this thought frightens him to his core.</string>
    <string name="s7_desc">Samuel is super strong and can withstand a tank\'s blast against him. Although his skin is
        as strong as titanium, he lacks combat abilities and knowledge.</string>
    <string name="pain_desc">Pain doesn\'t have powers or abilities, but he is very skilled in hand-to-hand combat
        and has an expertise in weaponry. He usually uses a sniper rifle, and mini-gun as a weapon. He wears a combat
        suit that hides his face.</string>
    <string name="massacre_desc">Once a kind, gentle and proud woman, Massacre is now filled with blood rage!
        She is pure evil now, and causes destruction wherever she is. While the innocent cower at the sight of her
        menace, an alien being named Nervo has taken a special interest in her.</string>
    <string name="nervo_desc">Nervo is a calm, collected individual who perseveres in patience. He\’d rather
        get to know his target, weaken them and strike when they are most vulnerable. It is an attribute he
        developed from fighting countless species on Helo.</string>
    <string name="dark_preistess_desc">Nysida is tired of those who only see the people of M\'ktor as a small group of
        weak people who only have healing abilities. She has vowed to increase her own power at any cost to prove to the
        world that M\'ktor is a place to be feared. Nysida will destroy all who get in her way of growing stronger
        and does not care who dies in the process.</string>
    <string name="tormented_king_desc">Elriush, once known for kindness, has truly become to epitomize the archetype of
        a Mad King. He transitioned into power with only glory in mind and is now only a shadow of his former self.
        Elriush is not fit to rule his people. He still holds the title of King of M\'ktor but he wanders their homeland
        in a ghastly fashion with little to no emotion.</string>
    <string name="exiled_priestess_desc">Lydae is hurt that her forested homeland of M\'ktor has been consumed by swampland,
        darkness and greed. She does not blame her father for her exile, but is instead saddened by how far he has fallen
        and how he has lost the light that their people once fought for. Fueled by nothing but misplaced love for her
        father and sister, Lydae strives to be like her mother and bring light back into the darkness.</string>
    <string name="psychick_desc">Evelyn Cherry loves to mess with other students during her free time, it amuses her.
        She loves to draw, and hang out with her friends. She generally remains optimistic, but does have a mean side to
        her that only surfaces under dire circumstances.</string>
    <string name="amusing_sinner_desc">Jackel\'s only gift is the gift of laughter. He is a master manipulator
        and can get anyone to do his bidding. However, the times when he does get his hands dirty the
        results are always gut wrenchingly disgusting!</string>
    <string name="brainz_desc">Alan is calm, and is a bit courageous. He is very smart, and due to being able
        to understand the world around him, he has always understood how his abilities work. But how Alan got
        his abilities remains unknown.</string>
    <string name="slade_desc">Slade does not speak much, but when he does it is straight to the point
        and meaningful. He cares mostly about nature and it\'s balance. He can sense when there is an
        imbalance between human consumption and destruction and the replenishing of nature in the world.</string>
    <string name="general_of_grins_desc">With his madness and disfigurements, BoBo relies on the troupes of Klown Krew
        members who spend their downtime either in padded cells or mockingly luring victims into the
        shadows where BoBo lurks. Simply, he is pure evil.</string>
    <string name="beast_girl">Ashley Blue is serious throughout life, and has no sense of humor. When she is turns
        into the Beast, she is unable to speak any words and can rarely control herself until she tires. As a human,
        she is a little girl who is scared all the time.</string>
    <string name="burn_streak_desc">Once Lina sets a goal, she obsessively works towards that goal. But this also
        works against her. When she is unable to obtain what she wants, she becomes blind with rage!</string>
    <string name="dragon_flame_desc">Huo Tian is subservient and loyal to whomever he is following, regardless of
        right or wrong. At times he can be temperamental and arrogant, but mostly he is quiet and always ready to
        set something (or someone) ablaze.</string>
    <string name="madam_frost_desc">Madam Frost loves ice and hates fire, although she can\'t fly, she can ski on ice
        to travel to where ever she needs to go. She is unable to find love due to her ability to freeze
        anything she touches. She sometimes sobs randomly hoping to fall in love. She has a sense of humor
        and loves to toy with her enemy.</string>
    <string name="hot_head_desc">He doesn\’t wear any special suit he just tries to wear what the kids wear that
        is popular in school. He tries to look as normal as he can. He can produce and control fire, manipulating
        it into various weapons, but his favorite is the sword. He also learned to create basketball sized
        fireballs that he can throw around with incredible precision and speed.</string>
    <string name="protector_desc">Protector remains modest and believes he is guided by God. He feels
        passionate about fighting evil and protecting the innocent, but he also knows that he isn\'t perfect.
        He just does his best to make a difference in his own special way.</string>

    <!-- Guardian descriptions -->
    <string name="alpha">Alpha</string>
    <string name="beta">Beta</string>
    <string name="omega">Omega</string>

    <!-- dialog options -->
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="confirm_logout">Are you sure you want to logout?</string>
    <string name="check_network">Sorry for the delay. We\'re having trouble connecting.
        Check your internet connection and we\'ll have you traveling shortly</string>
    <string name="successful_update_stats_title">Successfully Updated Stats (Bulk)</string>
    <string name="successful_update_stats_message">Base stats for all Guardians have successfully been updated.
        Make getGuardiansRQ to confirm the latest changes.</string>
    <string name="successful_update_guardian_title">Successfully Updated Guardians</string>
    <string name="successful_update_guardian_message">Affinity, card type and descriptions for Guardians have
        successfully been updated. Make getGuardiansRQ to confirm the latest changes.</string>
    <string name="successful_update_mission_title">Successfully Updated Mission Difficulty</string>
    <string name="successful_update_mission_message">Mission difficulty levels have successfully been updated.</string>

    <!-- error messages -->
    <string name="default_error_message">Sorry, we\'re having trouble connecting to our servers.
        Please check your connection and try again later.</string>
</resources>
